<tiltviewergallery>	<photos>		<photo imageurl="images/story1.jpg" showFlipButton="true">			<title>THE OBAMA EFFECT</title>			<description>Big changes in immigration policy are on the way - and regular people on both sides of the border will be affected in significant ways. We'll look at the way America's mid-eighties immigration amnesty program impacted people and communities, and explore the effect a new path-to-citizenship program might have on the country today. We'll also examine the current federal e-verify program and consider what its expansion might mean for employers and workers.			Video, photos, text, data, maps, user-generated content.</description>		</photo>		<photo imageurl="images/story2.jpg" showFlipButton="true">			<title>LOS CONVERSOS</title>			<description>Latinos are often thought of as deeply religious and devotedly Catholic.  But the Latino religious landscape is actually shifting rapidly.  Pentecostals, Mormons, and Jehovah's Witnesses have made huge inroads into the Latino community in the United States and abroad.  Some of these denominations have seen their biggest growth among Spanish speakers.  Many Latinos are also exploring their ancient religious roots and "re-converting" to Judaism. Meanwhile, the Catholic Church is making an effort to strengthen its ties to Latinos and even win back those who have joined other faiths.  We will look at this unexpected religious war for the hearts and souls of Latinos and explore the complicated relationships among the English and Spanish-speaking parishioners of traditionally "American" religions.			Video, text, data, maps, user-generated content.</description>		</photo>		<photo imageurl="images/story3.jpg" showFlipButton="true">			<title>AGAINST THE ODDS</title>			<description>The raw data on educational success among Latinos - especially immigrants - can be discouraging.  Economic and language barriers can be high hurdles. But some Latinos excel against all odds.  We will show you who these students are and how they succeeded.  Along the way we hope to discover some patterns and programs that can be used to help others.  What do these outstanding students do and how do educators, parents, and their community help them do it?  Some of the answers may surprise you.			Video, text, data.</description>		</photo>		<photo imageurl="images/story4.jpg" showFlipButton="true">			<title>LATINOS IN THE MILITARY</title>			<description>Joining the military is one of the most patriotic things a person can do. But what happens when significant numbers of "non-Americans" join the U.S. military? We'll examine the experience of Latinos who fight for the United States even though they're illegal immigrants - or considered non-American because of their skin color and Spanish surnames. We'll explore the issue through the eyes of veterans, active soldiers, recruiters and protesters. We will explore the contrasting ideas of patriotism espoused by "illegals" who risk their lives in the uniform of the American armed forces, and border security advocates who call for a military style "sealing" of the border.			Video, text, maps, data, user-generated content.</description>		</photo>		<photo imageurl="images/story5.jpg" showFlipButton="true">			<title>LIFE ON THE LINE</title>			<description>It can be difficult to explain the border to people who have never been there.  We will take our audience inside the lives of those who live and work along the line.  With a little help from us these people will tell their own stories.  What is it like to be deported?  What does the Mexican border patrol - Grupo Beta - do on a daily basis?  What does a U.S. Border Patrol detention center look, feel, and smell like? What motivates people to cross - and keep crossing - the line?  What is the relationship between those charged with securing the border and those trying to cross it?  What do people really do once they cross the border? How do people try to find lost family members who may have been killed, deported, or kidnapped?			Video, photos, text, data, maps, user-generated content.</description>		</photo>		<photo imageurl="images/story6.jpg" showFlipButton="true">			<title>TRADING PARTNERS</title>			<description>The United States and Mexico have a well-known - and sometimes controversial - economic trade relationship.  But we've learned some surprising things about non-economic trade.  Ideas and practices surrounding religion, fashion, music, sports, and art waft back and forth through the border region, creating interesting and highly unexpected cultural fusions. African-American hairstyles have popped up in Monterrey, Mexico.  The Virgin of Guadalupe - long a symbol of Mexican national pride - has taken the United States by storm, becoming a symbol of Latino pride and artistic experimentation.  We will look at these and other cases that show what happens with cultures cross and clash.			Photos, text, graphics.</description>		</photo>	</photos></tiltviewergallery>